女子監獄 第二季 第十集
老天爺
Oh, my God.
很差勁對嗎
Horrible, wasn't it?
最差勁了
The worst.
你這個做得真差勁
You're really bad at that.
讓我服務你好嗎
Can I do you?
你不必問
You don't have to ask.
我從來沒有過真正地...
I've never really...
為女人口交過嗎
Gone down on a woman before?
我是說
I mean...
沒有
No.
你算是哪門子的女同啊
What kind of a lesbian are you?
摸咪咪的
The boob-touching kind.
那好吧
All right, well...
你準備好"俯身"一試嗎
Are you ready to take the plunge...
可以這樣說
so to speak?
你會教我嗎
Are you gonna coach me through it?
當然
Yeah.
該死
Shit.
阿姆斯特丹現在幾點
What time is it in Amsterdam?
我不知道
I have no idea.
等我一下
Okay, um, give me a second.
對不起  生意上的事
I'm sorry, it's business.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
你要喝杯水嗎
Do you want a glass of water?
這也是反應之一嗎
Is that a part of it?
脫水
Hydration?
搞什么
What the...
艾麗克斯
Alex!
老天  你媽的搞什么
Jesus! What the fuck?
住手  西爾維
Stop, Sylvie!
-住手  西爾維  媽的  -婊子
- Stop it, Sylvie! Shit! - Bitch!
老天
Jesus.
她打我
She... she attacked me.
-你媽的開什么玩笑  -別這樣  帕波
- Are you fucking kidding? - Stop. Piper...
她就這樣闖了進來
She just broke in here.
我住在這里
I live here!
是的
She does.
這是我的女友  你這個婊子
That's my girlfriend, you whore.
不
No.
把她趕出去
Get her the fuck out of here.
我會的
Okay, I will. I'm gonna get
我會讓她走  然后我們談談
her out of here and then we're gonna talk.
我說了  讓她滾  立刻
I said, get her out! Now!
西爾維  別這樣  西爾維
Sylvie. Come on, Sylvie.
你的女友
Your girlfriend?
很復雜  帕波
It's complicated, Piper.
真操蛋
This is so fucked up.
對不起  我應該說的
I'm sorry, I should've said something.
你以為呢
You think?
你受傷了嗎  她打傷你了嗎
Are you hurt? Did she hurt you?
她揍了我的臉
She punched me in the face.
對  很痛
Yes, it hurts.
媽的  我另一只鞋呢
Fuck, where is my other shoe?
我只是  不斷見到你
I just... I kept seeing you around and...
我喜歡你  然后你打來電話
You know, I liked you, and then when you called...
閉嘴  別說了  你越描越黑
Okay, stop it. Please don't. You're making it worse.
給
Here.
你找到另一只鞋子了嗎
Did you find your other shoe?
算了
Forget it.
你沒鞋怎么走回家
What? You can't walk home without your shoes.
你的鞋子很漂亮
They're nice shoes.
馬歇爾百貨買的  操你媽
They're from Marshalls. Fuck you!
脫衣服
Strip.
你也早上好
Good morning to you, too.
你噴了香水嗎
You wearing perfume?
的確是的
I am, in fact.
我離開家前噴了點身體噴霧
I put on a little spritz right before I left the house.
你鼻子很靈
You have a good nose.
我有時會在耳后擦杏仁精
I put almond extract behind my ears sometimes.
讓我聞起來一股曲奇味
Makes me smell like a cookie.
別廢話了  下蹲咳嗽
Anyway, let's get to the squat and cough.
好的
Okay.
瞧瞧  她來啦
Well, well, there she is.
-浪子回來了  -是的
- The prodigal daughter returns. - Yep.
還沒到早上8點
It's not even 8:00 A.M.
我已經被揩了三次油了
And I've already been felt up three times.
-怎么樣  -摸奶頭摸得不夠
- How was it? - Not enough nipple play.
好笑
Funny.
這么說你不想談
So you don't wanna talk about it?
我還在慢慢接受中
I'm, uh, still processing, you know.
和老年人尷尬的交談
Awkward conversations with old people,
糟糕的干酪盤  葬禮
bad cheese plates, a funeral,
婚禮  麥芽啤酒
a wedding, malt liquor.
48小時體驗一輩子
A whole lifetime in 48 hours.
你知道什么感覺很奇怪嗎
You know what was so weird?
用非塑料的盤子吃東西
Eating off of plates that weren't plastic.
感覺好重
They felt so heavy.
你有空閑時間嗎
Did you by any chance have time?
我有
I did.
我有些不敢問
I'm afraid to ask.
很棒  非常棒
It was great. It was really great.
真是皇后區的一處好地方
And that is such a cute part of Queens.
我之前沒怎么去過
I've never spent much time there.
你進去了嗎
Did you go in?
時間不長
For a minute.
生意很好  還排了隊
You know, it's doing really well. There was even a line.
你點了什么嗎
But you ordered something?
點了  我...
Yes! I, um...
點了那種甜甜的
One of those... the sweet...
-乳酪面包嗎  -是的
- Vatrushki? - Yes.
-乳酪面包  -是的
我會在夏天用蜜桃泥做
I do them with peach puree in the summertime.
太好吃了
Delicious.
那地方真漂亮  紅媽
It's such a beautiful place, Red.
我明白你為什么為之如此驕傲
I can really see why you are so proud of it.
真的謝謝你
Thank you. Really.
我的兒子們告訴我生意很差
My boys had told me business was bad, and, you know,
在這里  我無能為力
from in here, there's nothing I can do.
感謝上帝有了轉機
Thank God they turned it around.
你和萊瑞怎么樣了
So, how was it with Larry?
奇怪  傷心  正式分手
Bizarre, sad, officially over,
他上了別人
and he fucked someone else.
他告訴你的嗎
He told you this?
在醉酒極度悲傷的性交過程中說的
In the middle of a drunken, grief-stricken sexual encounter.
你知道最奇怪的是什么嗎
But you know what the weirdest thing was?
我甚至一點也不生氣
I wasn't even mad. At all.
這也說得通  一報還一報
It kind of made sense. Tit for tat.
我們的情況是奶子換奶子
Or, well, tit for tit, as the case may be.
親愛的
Oh, honey,
你心胸比我寬廣
you're a bigger woman than I am.
-他上的誰  -我不想知道
- Who was it? - I didn't wanna know.
-少廢話  -真的  我不想知道
- Oh, bullshit. - No, really, I didn't wanna know.
他告訴我  是我認識的人
He told me it was someone I know,
知道是誰只會更糟
and a name would just make it worse.
你知道誰最有可能嗎  我們的鄰居娜塔利
But you know who it probably was? Our neighbor, Natalie.
她是瑜伽教練
She's a Bikram teacher.
很嗲那種
She's very touchy-feely,
總是讓我們去免費上課
she's always offering us lots of free classes.
但誰在乎啊  根本不重要
But who cares? It doesn't matter anyway.
我們分手了
We broke up.
是我先出軌的  不是嗎
I'm the one who cheated first, right?
你有信
Some mail came for you.
是沃斯寄來的
It's from Vause.
感謝你為我抽出時間
And thank you for taking the time for me.
回頭有漂亮的唇彩給你
You will be getting some very nice lip gloss.
別忘了  女士們
Don't forget, ladies,
正常飲食是1500卡路里
your usual meal is 1,500 calories.
不要暴食
Be aware of overeating.
有兩份華夫餅
There's two waffles on there.
你媽的在做什么
怎么啦  她們多給煙我抽
謝謝
Thank you.
有話要對我說嗎
You got something to say to me?
我的姑娘們需要你的座位
My girls need your seat.
我吃完后  她們就可以坐了
And when I'm done, they can have it.
吃完了嗎
Done yet?
你真是一個無禮的女人
You are a very rude woman.
人家傷心死了
Oh, you wound me.
媽的  維  咱在這里屌爆了
Yo, damn, Vee! Yo, we like ballers up in here!
我不是說了嗎  你能給別人所需時...
Didn't I tell y'all? When you got something people want...
今天早上
Yo, this morning,
爆牙克萊門蒂諾居然在浴室等我
Underbite Clementino was waiting for me in the bathroom
給我來個背部按摩
to give me a back massage.
-什么  -背部按摩
- What? - A back massage!
感覺我像是圣特魯佩斯一艘游艇上的碧昂斯
Like I'm fucking Beyonce in a yacht in Saint-Tropez, okay!
下雨吧  賤人們
Make it rain, bitches.
小賣部女王駕到
Commissary queen in the hizzy!
媽的  感覺真好
Fuck, this feels good.
我把常那里掃蕩了
I cleaned Chang out.
你什么都買走了
"You take-a the everything!
沒有東西給其他女士了
Nothing reft for the other ladies."
我不是說過嗎  維會照顧我們的
Yo, didn't I tell you that Vee was gonna take care of us?
制度關著我們  你就得找到應對的辦法
System work you, you got to find a way to work the system.
-阿門  -贊美主啊  哈利路亞
- Amen! - Gloria, hallelujah!
誰給你剪的頭發  丹妮塔嗎
Who cuts your hair? Danita?
當然不是
Hell, no!
我才不會讓那個屠夫拿著剪刀接近我
I wouldn't let that butcher near me with a pair of scissors.
我自己打理的
I do it myself.
別看后面  一團糟
Don't look at the back, it's a mess.
什么大場合
What's the occasion?
我兒子來看我
My son's coming to visit.
如果他沒注意到  你別生氣
Well, don't be upset if he doesn't notice.
男孩子蠢死了  他們永遠不會注意到這種事
Boys are stupid. They never notice things like that.
邁克爾很久沒見過我了
Michael hasn't seen me in a long time.
他從未來過
He's never come before.
為什么不來
Why not?
他很生氣
He was pissed off.
或覺得丟人  或兩者都有
Or ashamed. Or both.
是他舉報我的
He turned me in.
那你打算在探視
So, you're strangling him
開始還是結束時掐死他
at the beginning of the visit or at the end?
他只有12歲  非常憤怒
He was only 12 and angry.
他經歷了太多
He's been through a lot.
我會坐好  讓他發泄  把怨氣全發泄出來
I'm gonna sit back, let him vent. You know, get it all out.
要是我  就踢死他
Well, if it were me, I'd kick him to death,
但我們做父母的方式不同
but we all have our own way of parenting.
甘地這么做來抗議種姓制度
Gandhi did it to protest the caste system.
只有這樣才能有所改變
It's the only way to make a real difference.
你就省省吧
You're wasting your breath.
你無法說服這些人絕食的
You're not gonna convince this crowd not to eat.
她是對的
She's right.
這碗麥片味道像大團鼻屎
I mean, this oatmeal tastes like a bowl of chunky boogers,
但媽的不吃還不舒服了
but fuck if it isn't comforting to keep shoveling it in.
這么說  你們都很滿意現狀
So I suppose you're all happy with the way things are going?
你們覺得這座監獄的現狀非常好嗎
You think the conditions in this prison are perfectly fine?
聯邦政府的錢應該用在
That federal money should be
讓女人在滿是排泄物的隔間里洗澡
spent on making women shower in feces-soaked stalls
而她們反抗時卻要遭受身體虐待嗎
and face physical abuse if they resist?
來吧  簡·方達[影星]  來點香腸
Come on, Jane Fonda, have a little bit of sausage.
對  就一小口  你看起來臉色蒼白
Yeah, just a little bite. You look a bit pale.
已經多少天了
How many days has it been?
拜托  別煩她了
Come on, leave her alone.
修女
Sister?
我以為至少你會支持我
I thought you of all people would support me.
親愛的  這里又不是關塔那摩監獄
Oh, honey, it's not Guantanamo.
就是
Yeah!
讓一下  蘇蘇
Yeah, move over, Soso.
好吧  我一個人來
Fine. I'll do it alone.
你真是太無禮了
That is really disrespectful.
休假怎么樣  給我帶T恤了嗎
How was furlough? Did you bring me back a T-shirt?
真他媽的  妹子
Holy shit, dude.
說什么
Well, what's it say?
慢著  讓我猜猜
Wait, let me guess.
美女  抱歉我在芝加哥坑了你
"Hey, girl, uh, sorry I fucked you over in Chicago.
那是為你好  我給你舔陰戶吧
It was for your own good. Let me lick your pussy."
可能吧  但我不知道
Probably, but I don't know.
-我還沒看  -什么
- I haven't read it. - What?
老天  你意志真堅定啊
Man, that's some serious willpower right there.
你就不好奇嗎
Aren't you curious?
我當然好奇  這是第一封我沒扔掉的
Of course I'm curious. It's the first one I haven't thrown away.
那就看唄
So, fucking read it already.
-我來  -不用不用
- I'll do it. - No! No, no, no, no, no.
她就是想要這樣
That is exactly what she wants.
對  當人們寄信
Yes, that is generally what
一般就是想讓別人看
people want when they send a piece of correspondence.
她會說些什么我想聽的話
What could she possibly say that I want to hear?
她是個說謊精
She's a liar.
從最開始  她就滿口謊言
She's always been a liar. From the very beginning.
難道不是每個人都對每個人說謊嗎
Doesn't everyone lie to everyone?
她知道如果她一直寄信
She knows that if she keeps sending these,
最終會打動我
eventually I will crack,
然后她會道歉
and then she'll apologize,
然后她會滿口仁義  讓她去死
and she'll say all the right things, and fuck that!
但你也不會把信扔掉
But you're not gonna throw it away either.
-你想她  -我當然想她
- You miss her. - Of course I miss her.
我討厭她對我的影響力  我真是煩透了
I hate that she has this hold on me. I'm so sick of it.
麥片味道跟鼻屎一樣
The oatmeal tastes like snot.
我要一杯  要一杯
I'll take a... shot. Shot!
沒關系  我要這個
It's all good. Okay, I got this one.
太差勁了
Oh, that was terrible!
你怎么來了
What are you doing here?
我嘛
Oh, I just, um...
我聽說了艷舞表演
I heard about the burlesque show.
-你呢  -我朋友瑞秋是演員之一
- You? - My friend Rachel's in it.
她和雷·羅曼諾的木偶一起表演
She does this routine with a Ray Romano puppet.
居然相當性感
It's surprisingly sexy.
那晚的事我很抱歉  帕波
Look, I'm really sorry about that night, Piper.
我不是那種做事遮遮掩掩的人
I'm not a shady person.
算了  沒事的
Oh, come on, don't worry about it.
我以前沒挨過揍
I mean, I've never been punched before.
這可能是很好的人生體驗
It was probably a good life experience.
我說事情很復雜時是認真的
I meant it when I said that things were complicated.
戀愛關系對我來說是新嘗試  我不知道
I'm new to this whole relationship thing. You know, I don't...
我不知道規則
I don't know the rules.
這就是問題所在對嗎
That's the whole problem, isn't it?
守規矩一點也不好玩
Rules aren't any fun.
我不想打擾真愛
Listen, I don't want to stand in the way of true love.
如果那位是你未來的妻子
I mean, if that is your future wife out there,
請務必讓我走開
by all means, tell me to back off.
但你追求我  我很喜歡
But you pursued me, and I liked it.
我
I've...
我從未感受過...
I've never felt...
我從未覺得自己是個
You know, I've never really thought of myself
性欲很強的人  但是
as a very sexual person, but...
自從...
ever since...
我想品嘗你的味道
I want to taste what you taste like.
餐廳供應什么  紅媽
What were they serving in there, Red?
內臟[屈辱]餡餅
Humble pie?
鳥肉[大麻]  生奶油[鞭打]老太太
Crow? Whipped old lady?
一直在練習雙關冷笑話嗎
Been practicing those?
自大漢堡  臉上的雞蛋[恥辱]
High horse hamburger? Egg on your face?
你吃了你的帽子嗎[說過的話錯了]
Did you eat your hat?
-哥們  -嘿
- Hey, bud. - Hey.
還好不
How you doing?
你那次崩潰后  你那晚哭了沒
Did you cry it out the other night after your little lady meltdown?
拜托  兄弟  放輕松
Oh, come on, man, relax. Shit, loosen up.
就像我媽經常說的  別一臉苦逼樣
It's like my mom used to say, "Wipe that puss off your face."
直譯為"把陰戶從臉上拿開"
當然那是在我意識到  我喜歡臉貼著陰戶前
'Course that was before I learned I liked puss on my face.
又是新的一天  本尼特
It's a new day, Benerino.
這他媽算什么  《獄中號角》
What the fuck is this? The Big House Bugle?
顯然你支持這種犯人宣傳活動
Clearly you supported this prisoner propaganda.
她們為我寫了篇不錯的封面故事
They did a nice cover story on me.
你們這些白癡
And none of you morons
沒人看懂漫畫里的那只海象是海利嗎
caught on that the walrus in the comic is Healy?
我覺得很搞笑
I thought it was pretty funny.
你覺得這只穿高跟鞋
And who do you think is the pig in high heels
背著幾包錢的豬是誰
carrying around the bags of money?
真難住我了
You got me there.
這垃圾是誰負責的
Who's in charge of this garbage?
應該是查普曼  犯人主編
That would be Chapman. Inmate-in-chief.
我不想再見到這種爛東西
I don't want to see this shit again.
也許你應該重新考慮下
You might want to reconsider.
你會需要全部的新聞宣傳
You can use all the journalistic spin you can get.
為什么
Why?
你最喜歡的強奸犯警衛表現突出
Your favorite rapist guard has exceeded all expectations.
迪亞茨懷孕了
The Diaz girl is pregnant.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
今天早上做了檢查
Tested her this morning.
上帝
Jesus.
壞壞的孩子他爸
Big, bad baby daddy,
你讓他回來的
and you brought him back.
真他媽的  我得把握住局勢
Fuck me. I gotta get out in front of this.
不能讓門德斯知道這事  等我安排好再說
Mendez can't know anything until I frame the whole thing.
你讓他繼續工作嗎
You're keeping him at work?
等我把事情安排好
Just until I get my ducks in a row.
這事得正確解決
This thing has to be handled right.
你要我為你保守這個秘密
You want me to keep this under wraps,
你就得為我做點事
you're gonna have to do something for me.
什么
What?
到時候
When it's time...
我來炒掉這個雜種
I get to fire the bastard.
好
Fine.
為什么是俄國人
So, why a Russian?
我不知道  我只是
I don't know. I just...
我做了些網上調查
I did some online research,
發現最受歡迎的郵購網站
and I found that the top-rated mail order sites
不是東歐就是東方的  所以
were either Eastern European or Oriental, so...
我覺得和俄國人少些文化障礙
I figured there'd be less cultural barriers with the Russians.
有金錢交易嗎
And there was money exchanged?
對不起  我對這個不熟
I'm sorry, I'm not familiar with...
我不需要你對我品頭論足
You know, I don't... I don't need your judgment, okay?
因為就所見而言
'Cause from the looks of it, you know,
我想你的愛情生活也不怎么樣
I'm guessing your love life isn't so hot either.
也許你把你的經歷投射到我身上  山姆
Perhaps you're projecting your experiences onto me, Sam.
少說些心理學廢話
Let's cut the fucking psychobabble, okay?
我的老婆是我買來的  他媽的又怎樣
I have a wife that I paid for. So fucking what?
我不需要你搬出這些教課書術語
I don't need you going around throwing out these textbook
就像那些有優越感的偽百事通一樣
terms like some condescending know-it-all.
我也是靠這個吃飯的
This is what I do for a living, too.
我是個輔導員
I'm a counselor.
你為什么來這里
Why did you come here?
我他媽的也不知道為什么來這里
You know, I don't fucking know why I came here.
因為我他媽的不需要你的幫助
Because I don't need your fucking help.
因為我才是幫助他人的人
Because I'm the one that's helping people.
日復一日
All day long.
是嗎
Do you?
你真的幫助了他人嗎
Do you really help people?
他媽的當然了
You bet your ass I do.
老天  這些發辮癢死了
Man, these tracks itching something fierce.
我得把這些給維  讓她能散出去給她的人
I gotta get these to Vee so she can get 'em out to her people.
寄郵票需要多少郵票
How many stamps do you need to send stamps?
你有時間嗎
Yo, you got a second?
我知道你們在販毒
I know y'all are dealing.
那又如何
Yeah, so?
你對我說謊  T
So, you lied to me, T.
說得你好像沒賣過毒品一樣
Like you never sold drugs.
我賣的是大麻  不是那些害人的
I sold weed. Not real shit.
害人到足夠把你關在這里了
Real enough to get your ass locked in here.
別這么假清高
So don't be acting all high siddity.
怕你沒注意到
In case you ain't noticed,
這里全是罪犯
this place is full of criminals.
我們也是其中兩個
And we're two of 'em.
加那邊的瘋子有三個罪犯
Three, if you include cuckoo over here.
咱們有錢賺吶
Yo, we's getting paid, man.
咱們幫萬歲  警察去死
Our crew rules. Fuck the police!
現在你們全成了黑幫分子嗎
Oh, what, now you all gangster?
你們全他媽被洗腦了
Man, y'all are fucking brainwashed.
你嫉妒了
You're jealous.
嫉妒什么  你像個欺負人的小混混嗎
Jealous of what? You acting like a hood rat corner kid?
你不知道我的出身
You don't know where I come from.
我沒有老爸在軍隊  沒父母管我
I ain't have no daddy in the army, parents looking out for me,
沒有棉衣  你這個有錢人家的賤人
and a fucking winter coat, you bougie bitch.
別假裝你了解我和我的人
So don't pretend like you know me or my people.
我以為你不想墮落到如此地步
I thought you wanted to be better than that.
滾出我的鋪位
Get the fuck out of my bunk.
臨時檢查
Yo, it's a sweep.
他們臨時檢查
They sweeping.
快走  女士們
Let's go, ladies!
犯人們  立刻離開鋪位
Inmates, outside your bunks, now!
全部不準動
Don't move a muscle.
讓我看到你們吞什么藏什么
I see you swallow anything or tuck anything away,
就等著關禁閉吧
your ass goes to the box.
我想左邊拔得太夸張了對嗎
I think I did the left side too much. Right?
眉彎太高了嗎
The arch is too high?
看起來
Eh, it kind of looks like
你這人疑神疑鬼的
you're really skeptical about everything.
我覺得狡猾的樣子挺性感的
I think the leery look is hot, you know?
-A區宿舍  臨時檢查  -媽的
- A-Dorm! Sweep time! - Fuck!
他們會拿走我的唇膏
They're gonna take my lipstick.
臨時檢查  女士們
Sweep time, ladies!
媽的
Fuck!
真他媽的
Shit! Son of a...
犯人  出去
Inmate, outside!
非法食品  記一筆
Illegal foodstuffs. That's a shot.
指甲油  鋒利鑷子
Nail polish. Sharp tweezers.
你的通話時間沒有了  犯人
There goes your phone time, inmate.
中大獎了
Jackpot!
恐怕這個可不是超強吸引性衛生棉條
I doubt these are super absorbent, huh?
這是誰的床鋪  沃森
Whose bunk is this? Watson.
這些小卷賣多少錢
How much these little rollies going for, huh?
給自己找了點買賣嗎
Got yourself a little business?
沒有  長官
No, sir.
別跟我說什么沒有
Don't you "No, sir" me!
快把你的黑屁股挪到禁閉室去
You start marching your pretty black ass to the SHU.
我知道你有多喜歡那里
I know how much you love it in there.
快走
Move!
給我
I'll take that.
你收到了我的卡
You have my card.
孩子們很可愛對嗎
Kids are cute, right?
另一張準備買的卡是一只貓說"你喵完美"
It was between this or some cats that said, "You're purr-fect!"
是的
Yeah.
我的選擇是正確的
I made the right choice.
你看起來不同了
You look so different.
不知怎的更溫柔了  這是好事
Softer somehow. In a good way.
我讓你留著這個
I'm gonna let you keep that.
沒發現
Clear!
老天  瞧這一堆
Jesus, what a haul!
把這個撕開檢查毒品后我就帶它回家
I'm taking this home after I rip it open to check for drugs.
好可愛
It's adorable.
看這些東西
Look at all this stuff.
顯然是有門路弄進來的
There are some serious open channels here.
你聞一下
Here, smell this, would ya?
好難聞
Whoa, that's awful.
聞一下
Smell it.
大便味
Oh, it smells like poo.
全聞起來是大便味
Yeah, it all smells like poo.
知道這意味著什么嗎
You know what that means?
全是通過直腸弄進來的
It's all coming in through the rectal pipeline.
下蹲咳嗽檢查太松懈了
Someone has been slacking with the squat and cough.
知道這意味著什么嗎
You know what this means?
光看已經不夠了  得開始捅了
It's not enough to look, we gotta start probing.
不能碰她們  這是違法的
We can't touch 'em. It's illegal.
我可不會把胳膊伸過去
I'm not sticking my arm up there.
那么伸手指呢  有什么不行
What about a finger? What's wrong with that?
偶爾伸根手指感覺不錯啊
A finger's nice once in a while.
只能目測
Visual inspections only.
小小的指頭  拜托
Tiny little finger? Come on.
我不知道你們  但我準備好做英雄了
I don't know about you all, but I'm ready to be the hero.
沒什么能逃過我
Nothing's getting past me.
你看的和你想的不一樣  就這樣了
You didn't see what you thought you saw, end of story.
-那是什么  -老天  有完沒完
- What was it, then? - Oh, Jesus, really?
我不會就此罷休的
Look, I'm not gonna leave you alone.
我什么也沒做
I'm not doing anything.
你要和我一起去廁所嗎
Do you wanna join me in the bathroom?
我要去那里  去拉屎
'Cause that's where I'm headed. To take a dump.
來吧  你可以把紙折整齊了給我
Come on, you can hand me neatly folded squares of paper
就好像你是宮廷侍從官  我是亨利八世
like you're the groom of the stole and I'm Henry VIII.
你給你今天的心理狀態打幾分
Well, how would you rate your state of mind today?
4嗎
A four?
你有沒有憤怒的想法  這種想法定期出現嗎
You having any angry thoughts? They coming up regularly for you?
Are you having angry thoughts that are coming up regularly?
這是投射
That's projection.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你知道我是靠什么維生嗎  我的工作是什么
You have any idea what I do for a living? What my job is?
我當然知道
Of course I do.
你為那些記過的女士們填寫相關文件
You fill out the paperworks for the ladies that get shots.
我提供指導
I provide guidance.
我就人們的問題提出忠告
I counsel people with their problems.
我想創辦一個支持小組
I'm thinking about starting a support group.
開展心理治療
It's a therapy thing.
我覺得對這里的女性有幫助
I think the women here could really use it.
這里有些愛生氣的賤人
There are some angry bitches around here.
但如果沒有好處
But you know that ain't nobody gonna do nothing
是沒人會理的
without getting something from it.
她們會有收獲的
They will be getting something.
對她們的問題有幫助
Help with their problems.
不  我是說比如免費甜甜圈  不用干活
No, I'm talking about, like, free donuts, or days off work.
我印了些傳單
I've, uh, printed out some flyers.
我想要你發出去
I'd like you to distribute them.
好的  海利先生
All right, Mr. Healy,
但我告訴你  沒人會來的
but I'm telling you, no one's gonna come on their own.
你低估了她們
You're underestimating them.
這些女性經歷了太多
These women have been through a lot.
她們會來的
They'll come.
沒想到你們會對文學有興趣
Didn't realize y'all had such literary interests.
我們希望你能給些建議
Yeah, well, we were hoping you could make a few suggestions.
因為我聽說  你這個人很會提意見
'Cause from what I hear, you're quite the little critic.
-我有些想法  -是嗎
- Yeah, I got some thoughts. - Yeah?
還有些問題
Yeah, and some questions.
你為什么讓珍娜被關了禁閉
Like why you let my girl Janae get dragged off to seg.
她應該明白不能把違禁品放在鋪位上
Well, she knew better than to keep contraband in her bunk.
現在她有許多獨處的時間來考慮這個問題
Guess she got a lot of alone time now to think about it.
她不會有事的  只要她只想不出聲
She'll be fine, so long as she thinks and doesn't speak.
你到底入不入伙
You in or out?
圖書館對我們來說是個好地方
The library is prime real estate for us.
你有地盤了  別在這里交易
Look, you got your spot. Deal out of there.
女囚們扎堆去倉庫是說不通的
There's no reason for the inmates to flow through the warehouse.
連看看都是不對勁的
There's no excuse to browse.
而且  警衛已經嗅到了血腥味
Plus, the hacks got a taste of blood.
他們檢查所有的工作地點只是時間問題
It's only a matter of time before they sweep all the work sites.
我不是小混混
I ain't no corner girl.
我喜歡這個地點
I like this spot.
所以你要么聽話  要么要求調職
So you either get your ass in line or request a transfer.
我聽說電工那邊在招人
I hear Electrical is looking.
明白嗎
You feel me?
我哪里也不去
I ain't going nowhere.
明白嗎
You feel me?
迪亞茨女士  我們只是需要口頭確認
Miss Diaz, we just need verbal confirmation
門德斯警官強暴了你  你能說出來嗎
that Officer Mendez forced himself on you. Can you provide that?
你沒看到嗎
Didn't you see it?
這是為了文書工作
This is for our paperwork.
喬  如果你不在這里
Joe, I think Miss Diaz would be more comfortable
我想迪亞茨女士會自在些
if you weren't in the room.
有法律規定
Look, there are laws in place
犯人與監獄工作人員的性愛是非法的
which criminalize sex between prisoners and prison staff.
這意味著工作人員有性愛不當行為時
Which means that employees who engage in sexual misconduct
不能將對方同意作為辯護借口
cannot claim consent as a defense.
所以正式來說這是強奸
So, officially it's a rape,
沒錯  我們會這么說
yes, and we're all gonna call it that.
但我需要知道  女人對女人
But I need to know, girl-to-girl...
是你情我愿的嗎
was it consensual?
我明白  你孤單  你想調調情
Listen, I get it. You're lonely, you want to flirt a little.
引起警衛的注意令你覺得很特別
Attention from a guard makes you feel special.
僅是那身制服就讓人有性趣對嗎
I mean, those uniforms alone can be a real turn-on, right?
就咱們之間說清楚
So, just between us,
我要知道你是否鼓勵了他
I need to know if you encouraged him.
-是的  -我想也是
- Yes. - I thought as much.
你真給我惹了大麻煩  小姑娘
Well, you've created quite a headache for me, young lady.
現在我不僅要對你負責
And now not only am I responsible for you,
還要對你肚中的胎負責
but for your little spawn of the system.
所以幫個忙  親愛的
So, do me a favor, sweetheart,
從現在開始  把你的雙腿閉緊
from now on, keep your legs closed.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你正式毀了一個男人的生活
You've officially destroyed a man's life.
不  你得告訴她  如果銀行周日關門
No, you gotta tell her that if the bank is closed on Sunday,
那么周一早上給她錢就他媽的沒有滯納金
that there's no fucking late fee if you pay her Monday morning.
-這種屁話不對  -我說了
- That shit's not right. - I did.
她依然要收你錢嗎
And she's still trying to charge you?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
你要這樣做
Okay, so here's what you gotta do.
你找根棒球棒
You get a baseball bat,
木頭的  不要金屬的
the wood kind, not the fucking metal kind,
一個大垃圾袋
and a big trash bag,
黑色的  不要看得透那種
the black kind, not the see-through kind...
邁克爾  你長大了
Michael, you look all grown up.
你一定長高了有4英寸
You must have grown, like, 4 inches.
現在叫邁克了
It's "Mike" now.
看看他的腳
Now, take a look at his feet.
我告訴他  他躺下去和站著一樣高
I told him he's as tall lying down as he is standing up.
你想對我說什么
Anything you want to say to me...
都可以  明白嗎
you can say it, okay?
也許我們應該玩游戲  好嗎
Well, you know, maybe we should play a game. Hmm?
那邊小孩用品里有撲克牌  怎么樣
They got a deck of cards over there by the kids' stuff. Huh?
在探視室  可以擁抱兩次
When in the Visitation Room, you're allowed two hugs,
到達和離開時分別一次
one on arrival and one on departure.
衛生間還沒修好
Well, they still didn't fix the bathrooms,
湖邊應該建擋土
and they were supposed to put in a retaining wall by the lake,
但現在只有幾包沙袋
but there's just a couple of sandbags.
我查了FCP這個名字  并不存在
Well, I ran the name FCP and it doesn't exist.
查不到這家公司
No trace of the company.
你確定在卡車上看到的是這個名字嗎
You sure that's the name you saw on the truck?
對  我肯定
Yeah, I'm positive.
我猜想
Well, my guess is that the
監獄給合同的公司
prison is giving inflated contracts to companies
要么是空殼公司  要么是菲茨核心的下屬公司
that are either shells or subsidiaries of FitzCORE,
菲茨核心將回扣
and FitzCORE is paying
給杰森·菲格羅亞的競選
kickbacks into the Jason Figueroa campaign.
我需要的是發票  我能看出誰在拿錢
What I need are invoices, so I can see who's getting paid.
是哦
Right.
不如這樣
Well, what about...
不如拍些未完成品的照片
What about photos of all the unfinished work?
如果我能給你弄部相機
If I could get you a camera...
不  不如你給我弄部蘋果手機
No, why don't you get me an iPhone
這樣我能拍照  還能玩"糖果大爆險"
so then I can take pictures and play Candy Crush?
你瘋了嗎
Are you insane?
我之前跟你說過了
I told you before,
我不會以自由為代價  為你的署名文章冒險
I'm not risking my freedom for your fucking byline.
帕波  這個女人是罪犯
Piper, this woman is a criminal.
是嗎  我也是
Yeah? Well, so am I.
要二嗎
Collecting twos?
不要
Nope.
對我有用
Better for me.
你確定嗎
You sure about that?
你把我打得落花流水
You're kicking my ass here.
對  到我發牌了
Yep. My turn to deal.
謝謝
Thank you.
南斯先生  你怎么來了
Mr. Nance, what brings you here?
菲格羅亞女士  你好嗎
Miss Figueroa, how are you?
知道你來我監獄做什么我會更好
Better once I know what the fuck you're doing in my prison.
我來探視一位朋友
I was... visiting a friend.
那位朋友是誰
And what friend might that be?
我給你的辦公室打過幾個電話
You know, I've called your office a bunch of times.
是嗎
Have you?
我五秒鐘就能找出你在誰的探視名單上
I can find out whose list you're on in five seconds flat,
沒必要玩游戲
so there's no need to play games here.
帕波·查普曼
Piper Chapman.
帕波·查普曼  你怎么認識她的
Piper Chapman. And how do you know Piper Chapman?
我們有共同的朋友
We have... mutual friends.
你看到這爛人了嗎
You seeing this shit?
就好像他媽的看上我一樣
I mean, it's like she's got a fucking hit out on me.
我想她要你的芝士泡芙
I think she wants some of those cheese puffs you got.
給她一點吧
Maybe just give her a few.
一定是這樣  她看上我的泡芙了
Oh, yeah, that must be it. She's after my puffs.
莫里洛  你有探視者
Morello, you have a visitor.
到探視室報到  莫里洛
Report to Visitation, Morello.
是你啊  妹子
That's you, kid.
應該沒人來看我啊  也許是我的妹妹
I'm not expecting anybody. Maybe it's my sister.
老天  希望沒出事  我樣子如何
Jeez, I hope there's nothing wrong. How do I look?
-漂亮  -好的
- Looking hot. - All right.
你夠了
Stop!
至少進來讓我可以看到你
Man, or at least get in here where I can see you.
你打算做這種無聊事做多久
How much longer is this shit gonna go on for?
你要拿去給紅媽
You need to take it to Red.
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你真覺得我會為了嗨一次
You really think I'm gonna throw
丟掉兩年的戒毒成果嗎
away two years of sobriety for one little high?
我看到崔希婭被裝在運尸袋中被運出去
I saw Tricia get wheeled out of here in a body bag.
你覺得我有多蠢
How stupid do you think I am?
你好
Well, hello. Hi.
別碰我
Don't you fucking touch me.
坐下
Sit down.
很高興見到你  我喜歡你的毛衣
It's nice to see you. I like your sweater.
聽我說
Listen to me.
我知道你闖進了我家
I know you broke into my house.
我不知道你如何做到的  但你做到了
I don't know how you did it, but you did.
警察不相信我  但我知道是你
Now, the cops don't believe me, but I know it was you.
我不明白  你為什么來這里
I don't understand. Why did you come here?
因為我要聽你承認
Because I want to hear you say it.
-告訴我是你  -我不知道你在說些什么
- Tell me it was you. - I don't know what you're talking about.
顯然你坐牢這段時間
So, clearly your time in prison
并沒有讓你回歸現實  你這個瘋子
has done nothing to bring you back into reality, you psycho.
我對天發誓
I swear to God...
如果你再接近我  或是我的家人我的妻子
if you come near me, or my family, or my wife again, ever,
我會殺了你
I will kill you.
我會用雙手  活活掐死你
With my bare fucking hands, I will choke you until you are dead.
你能小點聲音嗎
Could you keep your voice down just a little?
你有病嗎  為什么
You... Are you out of... Why?
你讓我小點聲
You want me to keep my voice down
這樣你的罪犯朋友不會知道
so your criminal friends in here won't know that you're a
你是個瘋子  越獄跟蹤我嗎
mental case who broke out of prison to stalk me?
是他嗎
Is that him?
什么意思
What is that?
你要繼續玩這種瘋子把戲嗎
Are you trying to keep up this lunatic charade?
-假裝我是你男友嗎  -不是
- Pretend that I'm your boyfriend? - No.
我不認識這個女人  明白嗎
I don't know this woman, okay?
我們約會過一次  就一次
We went on one date! One!
她是個該死的跟蹤狂
She's a fucking stalker!
先生  請馬上離開
Sir, you need to leave now.
她是個危險人物
She's fucking dangerous!
-馬上離開  -她...
- Leave, now. - Hey... She...
你知道她越獄了吧
You know she broke out of here, right?
她是個瘋婊子
She's a psycho bitch!
-對不起  -快走
- Sorry. - Come on.
我可不是有罪的那個
Hey, man, I'm not the criminal here, okay?
我瘋了
I'm crazy.
我是個瘋子  我真的很有問題
I'm a crazy person. There is something really wrong with me.
我們所有人都有問題
I mean, there's something wrong with all of us.
否則我們不會在這里
Like, otherwise we wouldn't be in here.
不  我做了壞事
No, I did something bad.
非常壞
Really bad.
我應該待在醫院時
When I was supposed to be at the hospital,
我偷了車
I stole the van
去了他奧爾巴尼的家
and I went to his house in Albany.
你說真的嗎
Are you serious?
你知道如果你被抓的話會有什么后果嗎
Do you know what could happen if you got caught?
我想他們會控告你重罪潛逃
I think they charge you with felony escape.
刑期延長三倍
Triple your sentence.
我知道  相信我  我知道
I know. Believe me, I know.
別他媽的再這樣做了  你這個瘋子
Well, don't fucking do that again, you maniac.
真的
Seriously.
你沒被抓真是奇跡
It's a miracle that you didn't get caught.
我只是想見他
I just wanted to see him.
但他好惡毒  真的好惡毒
But he is so mean. I mean, he's really mean.
他不是我以為的那個人
He's not the man that I thought he was.
你恨我嗎
Do you hate me?
不  我不恨你
No, I don't hate you.
但每一秒
Well, it is getting clearer
都越來越清楚你是個瘋子
every second that you're totally bat-shit crazy,
但你是個美麗可人的女生
but you're a beautiful, sweet girl.
別去管這男人了  會有好多人愛你的
Fuck this guy. So many people are gonna love you.
不  沒人會愛我
No. No, nobody's gonna love me.
我愛
I do.
過來
Come here.
萊瑞  是我
Hi, Larry. It's me.
我知道我說過
Listen, I know that I said
我不想知道是誰  我的確不想
I didn't wanna know who it was, and I didn't.
但在這里  就是會讓人產生執念
But being in here, it just has a way of making you obsess
感覺有點瘋狂
and feel a little crazy.
嫉妒
Jealous.
我知道這樣不公平  但這是我的感覺
So, I know this is totally unfair, but it's how I feel.
所以我想如果我知道會好些
So I just think it would be better if I knew.
如果我知道是誰  我就不用再猜了
If I just knew who it was, and then I could stop guessing.
你的通話時間到了
Your phone time is up.
我剛剛...
I... I'm just...
再見
Um, bye.
這樣就對了
That's right.
走人吧
Move along.
反正我也講完了
I was done anyway.
我不是同性戀  我不是
I'm not gay. I'm not.
我只是在嘗試
I'm just experimenting.
我不知道
I don't know.
也許一直以來我交往的男人
Maybe all of the guys that I've been with so far
在床上表現都很差
have just been really bad in bed,
但我告訴你
but I'm telling you,
就好像我剛發現性愛應該是什么樣子
it's like I just discovered what sex is supposed to be.
-但她有女友  -是啊
- But she has a girlfriend? - Mmm...
她之前有女友
She had a girlfriend.
她們之間有問題  已經結束了
They were having problems. It's over.
-肯定嗎  -是的
- For sure? - Yeah.
我不確定  帕波
I don't know, Piper.
是誰
Who is that?
我的天  我的天  袋里有屎
Oh, my God. Oh, my God! There's shit in that bag!
你居然被騙了  這可是最古老的惡作劇了
You fell for that? That's like the oldest trick in the book.
什么是最古老的惡作劇
What is the oldest trick in the book?
屎在袋子里  點起火嗎
Poop? In a bag? On fire?
我哥和他的朋友以前經常這樣做
Yes, my brother and his friends used to do it.
真他媽的蠢  純粹惡作劇
It's so fucking stupid. It's a prank.
老天
Oh, my God.
-是她  -誰
- It's her. - Who?
-西爾維  艾麗克斯的前女友  -真的嗎
- Sylvia. Alex's ex. - Really?
她是個瘋婆子  她打了我
Yes, she's fucking crazy. She attacked me.
這是她做的  我知道
This is... This is her, I know it.
你覺得這是人屎嗎
Do you think it's human shit?
不  這是狗屎  對嗎
No, I mean, this is... This is dog shit, right?
如果她真的有你說的這樣瘋
I mean, if she's really as crazy as you say...
你不會覺得這是她蹲下拉在袋子里的吧
You don't think that she squatted and pooped in a bag, do you?
她的意思表達得很清楚了  佩服佩服
Well, she did get her point across. I'll give her that much.
女同都是瘋子
Lesbians are insane.
我不敢相信她對你說這種話  好大的膽子
I can't believe she said that to you. The fucking nerve! Jesus.
她是對的
She was right.
我引誘了他  我們故意陷害他
I seduced him. We set him up.
但她不知道
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
這樣不對  他會坐牢  約翰
It's wrong. He's going to jail, John.
有其它辦法嗎  怎樣  你想讓我...
What is the alternative? What, you want me to...
你想讓我站出來大聲說
You want me to stand up and shout,
各位  她肚里是我的寶寶
"Hey, everyone, that's my baby in there"?
在我生活的地方
You know, in my neighborhood,
真男人會站出來承認自己的孩子
real men stand up and claim their kids.
我們不是在你生活的地方  不是嗎
We're not in your neighborhood, are we?
你到底想要我怎樣  達婭
I mean, what the fuck do you want from me, Daya?
我要你站出來告訴全世界你愛我
I want you to stand up and tell the world that you love me.
這太瘋狂了
That is insane.
他們會把我推到媒體的峰尖浪口
They would cart me off in front of the local news.
-你想要這樣嗎  -不  是的
- Is that what you want? - No. Yes.
我不知道我想要什么  只是感覺很糟糕
I don't know what I want. It just feels really bad.
達婭  我會坐牢的
Daya, I would go to jail.
那樣至少我們扯平了
Well, then at least we'll be even.
如果你是來嘲笑我的  我可沒力氣吵
If you're here to mock me, I don't have the energy to argue.
做什么都痛
Everything hurts.
我不是來取笑你的
I'm not here to make fun of you.
是嗎
Really?
我昨天看到一位朋友被拉去關禁閉
I watched a friend get taken to the SHU yesterday.
那是她第二次被關禁閉
That's the second time she's been in there,
第一次很痛苦
and the first time was rough.
我已經厭惡厭倦了警衛把關禁閉
I'm sick and tired of the guards using solitary
當作是罰小孩子站晲
like it's some kind of toddler timeout.
這些人不是暴力罪犯
These are not violent offenders.
這是不人道的  這是折磨
It's inhumane and it's torture.
我覺得你這樣做  非常非常勇敢
I think what you're doing is very, very brave.
你是個真正的維權分子
You are a true activist.
你把我給你的傳單發完了嗎
Did you hand out all the flyers I gave you?
當然了  發了  長官
'Course I did. Yes, sir.
但我覺得沒人會...
But I really don't think anybody's gonna...
我知道  德蓋特  我明白
I know, Doggett. I got it.
-波麗  -你好
- Hey, Pol! - Hi.
老天  你好苗條
Oh, my gosh, you're so skinny.
你懷孕的肥屁股已經沒有了
Your big pregnancy ass is gone!
我知道
I know.
抱歉好久沒見了
I am so sorry it's been so long.
帕波  塞萊斯特的事我很遺憾
And, Pipe, I'm sorry about Celeste.
我應該去參加葬禮的  我只是
I should have been at the funeral. I just...
我的奶不多  擠奶太痛苦了
I'm not making that much milk, and pumping is really hard.
萊瑞說你現在是個二十四孝老媽
Larry says you've been lost in the baby fog.
我感覺好糟糕
I feel horrible.
你失去了親人  我應該在你身邊的
You lost someone. I should have been there for you.
真是對不起
I'm so, so sorry.
-我真是太差勁了  -別說了  沒關系
- It was really shitty of me. - Stop, it's fine.
不  有關系
It's not. It's not fine.
你需要我我卻不在  我是個差勁的朋友
You needed me and I wasn't there. I've been a really bad friend.
最差勁的朋友  你不應該有我這樣的朋友
Like, the worst. You don't deserve that.
你不應該經歷這些
You don't deserve any of this.
-當媽的感覺如何  -好難
- How is mommy life? - Hard.
比任何人講的都難多了
It's so much harder than anyone tells you.
我覺得我失去理智了  我不再是自己了
I feel like I've lost my mind. I'm not myself.
-皮特還好嗎  -皮特去了阿拉斯加
- Is Pete being good? - Pete took off to Alaska.
好奇怪  他太煩人了
It was weird and totally horrible of him.
你經常見萊瑞嗎
Have you seen Larry a lot?
沒有  為什么問  他說的嗎
No. Why, did he tell you that?
只是皮特離開期間
I mean, just when Pete was gone.
芬恩的事他幫了我不少
He helped me a lot with Finn.
你們還經常通話嗎
Are you guys still talking a lot?
我們剛在一起整整48小時
Well, we just spent the past 48 hours together.
怎么樣
How did that go?
我們做愛了
We had sex.
我們開始了  在給我奶奶守靈時
Well, we started to. At my grandmother's wake.
是嗎
Really?
你很驚訝嗎
Does that surprise you?
是啊  我以為你和他結束了
Uh, well, yeah, I thought you ended things.
他曾經是我的未婚夫  波麗  還是有愛的
He was my fiance Polly. There's still a lot of love there.
當然
Of course.
他和別人上過床了
He slept with someone else.
是嗎
Really?
他告訴你了嗎
Did he tell you that?
沒有  他為什么會告訴我
No, why would he tell me that?
你們一直有聯系
You two... have been talking.
你們關系好  他幫你照顧芬恩
You're close. He's been helping you with Finn.
我們關系也沒那么好
Oh, we're not that close.
他跟你怎么說的
Um... what did he tell you?
是我認識的人
That it was someone I know.
我想他感覺相當內疚
I think he was feeling pretty guilty.
他可能覺得那是一個錯誤
He probably felt like it was a mistake.
他不想傷害你
He doesn't want to hurt you.
我相信他不想
I'm sure that he doesn't.
你覺得她會謀殺我嗎
Do you think she's gonna murder me?
這個西爾維到底有多不正常
Just how unstable is this Sylvia person?
-那是個玩笑  -那不是玩笑
- It was a joke. - It was not a joke!
那是個意思很清楚的口信
It was a very clear message.
我知道你做了什么  婊子
"I know what you did, bitch,
我要你知道我知道了
and I want you to know that I know."
和你在一起是我的選擇
Look, being with you was my choice.
我之前不開心
I wasn't happy.
然后我利用了這點
And then I took advantage of that.
我是個成年人  帕波
I'm a grown-up, Piper.
你覺得她會來找我麻煩嗎
Do you think that she's gonna come after me?
我覺得她需要的是
Look, I think that she needed to
發泄出來  明白嗎
get it out of her system, all right?
有時候需要大怒一下才能放下
Sometimes you gotta rage in order to move on.
你愛過她嗎
Did you love her?
沒有
No.
但我愛你
But I love you.
真的嗎
You do?
這話我可不是隨便對每個人說的
I don't say that to everyone.
你得回應我
You have to say it back.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
你想談談嗎
Do you wanna talk about it?
不
No.
還記得我告訴你  我未婚夫干了別的女人嗎
Remember I told you that my fiance fucked somebody else?
是的
Yeah.
是我最好的朋友
It was my best friend.
請讓我一個人待下好嗎
Can I be alone for a minute, please?
當然  親愛的
Sure, honey.
親愛的  自己喝下毒藥是不可能殺死敵人的
Honey, you don't drink poison and wait for it to kill your enemy.
別再捶暀F  計劃復仇吧
Stop hitting walls and plot your revenge.
媽的
Oh, fuck!
你他媽的在做什么
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
我想加入你的園藝俱樂部
You know, I think I'd like to join your little gardening club.
我們不接受新會員
We're not accepting new members.
挖隧道嗎  紅媽  你以為你是兔八哥啊
A tunnel, Red? That is so Bugs Bunny.
你打算怎么做  出賣我嗎
What are you gonna do, turn me in?
不  我會用上這個
No, I'm gonna use it.
你有你自己的門路
You have your own operation.
我知道  但這個更好
Yeah, I know, but this is better.
更少的人參與  沒有不穩定的供貨聯系
Fewer people involved and no unstable vendor connections.
-不可能歸你  -不是的
- You're not taking it. - No, no, no, no, no.
我可不想奪走你的姑娘們的
I wouldn't want to deprive your girls
屎味的連褲襪
of their shit-flavored panty hose.
我們可以分享
We could share.
你不懂如何分享
You don't know how to share.
只會搶奪  只會欺凌弱小
Just to take and to bully.
我們曾經做過朋友
We used to be friends once.
我想再和你做朋友
I want to be friends again, man!
好個朋友
Some friend.
你會考慮下嗎
Will you think about it, huh?
你也想想這些年你變了多少好嗎
And would you think about how much you've changed over the years?
人會變  紅媽
People change, Red.
妮琪
Nicky.
你覺得人會變嗎
Do you think people can change?
好了
All right.
你把這個幫我拿走  因為我會吸
I need you to take this from me, 'cause I'm gonna do it.
但我真的真的不想
And I really, really don't want to.
誰給你的
Who gave that to you?
美味姐  維的貨
Taystee. It came from Vee.
真是對不起  紅媽  我讓你失望了
I'm so sorry, Red. I let you down.
-你沒有  -是嘛
- No, you didn't. - Yeah.
你拿來了
You brought it here.
你做得非常好  妮琪
You did good, Nicky.
你做到了
You did.
姑娘  穩著點
Hey, girl, steady there.
我很好  我沒事
I'm fine. I'm good.
-維  -啥事
- Yo, Vee! - Yeah.
-操你媽  -媽的  妹子  你喝醉了
- Fuck you. - Oh, shit, girl, you blind drunk.
你要搶走我的工作
You want to take my fucking job assignment?
你要搶走我所有的朋友  操你媽
You want to take all my friends? Well, fuck you!
在她傷到自己之前  來個人把她弄走吧
Somebody get her out of here before she hurts herself.
操你媽
Fuck you!
媽的
Shit!
操你媽
Fuck you!
-媽的  -你別碰她
- Fuck! - Don't you touch her!
不不
No! No! No!
你不聽話就會是這個下場
That's what you get when you don't listen!
就會是這個下場
That's what you get!
不
No.
喂
Hello?
利奇菲爾德聯邦監獄的女犯打來電話
An inmate from Litchfield Federal Prison is attempting to contact you.
要接聽電話  請按一
To accept this call, please press "One."
-卡爾的電話  -內莉  卡爾在嗎
- Cal's phone. - Neri, hey, is Cal there?
他去樹林覓食去了
No, he's out foraging in
去找吃起來有蔬菜味的蔬菜
the forest for greens that taste really green.
但他可能已經快好了  要我叫他嗎
But he's probably almost done. Should I go get him?
也許你能幫我
Actually, maybe you can help me.
好啊  小姑子
Yeah, sister-in-law!
什么忙都行
Whatever you need, dude.
我需要你幫我一次
I need you to do me a favor.
一個大忙
It's a big one.
我活該
I deserve that.
-好啦  -嘿
- All right. - Hey.
我為你驕傲
I'm proud of you.
那就快滾
Then get the fuck out of here.
-什么事  -沒什么
- What was that about? - Nothing.
你有沒有見過一種畫面  會烙在你的腦海里的
You ever seen an image that sears itself into your brain?
就像那部講驢友的電影
Like the movie about the hiker guy,
他用瑞士軍刀把自己的胳膊給切斷了
where he cuts off his own arm with a Swiss Army knife?
那個聲音  肌腱
Yeah, the sound, the tendons...
媽的
Fuck!
我真希望自己沒看過那部分
I wish I never watched that part.
你知道什么讓我覺得更惡心嗎
You know what tops that for me?
什么畫面讓我忘不掉  在腦海里揮之不去
You know what image I can't unsee, it's still stuck in there,
一天至少想到一次  讓我沒胃口吃午飯
flickering at least once a day, making me want to lose my lunch?
不知道  先生
No, sir.
你的光屁股  門德斯
Your bare ass, Mendez.
你那長疙瘩的蒼白屁股
Your pimply, white ass,
在掃把拖把間上上下下
bouncing up and down between the brooms and the mops,
撞擊那可憐的姑娘
ramming into that poor girl.
一個你本應保護保障她安全的姑娘
A girl you were supposed to protect and keep safe.
你的屁股  像鬼一樣纏著我
Your ass, it haunts me.
抱歉聽到這個  先生
I'm sorry to hear that, sir.
我做這行已經25年了
I've been doing this kind of work 25 years.
就是像你這樣的人  給了這份職業一個壞名聲
And it's guys like you that give the whole profession a bad name.
如果我說了算
If it was up to me,
你永遠別再想涉足這個地方
you'd never set foot on this property again.
但考慮到懲教署不提出起訴
But considering the DOC didn't press charges,
之前只是我們間的言語之爭
it was your word against mine...
直到現在
until now.
我一直在本分工作  先生
Well, I've been doing my job, sir.
今天早上就記了15個過了
Just gave out 15 shots this morning.
你讓她懷孕了
You got her pregnant.
不
No.
對她來說很不幸  是的
Sadly for her, yes.
那個可憐的姑娘懷上了
That poor girl is carrying around
一個大胡子虐待狂的孽種
a sadistic little mustachioed shit inside her.
-哇  -門德斯
- Whoa. - Mendez...
你他媽的被炒了
you're fucking fired.
我明白  先生
I understand, sir.
不  我想你沒明白
No, I... I don't think you do understand.
你還被逮捕了
You're also under arrest.
我們到了
We're in.
我來吧
Let me get that for ya.
好了  咱們走
All right, let's go.
我們在利奇菲爾德聯邦監獄現場報導
We're reporting from Litchfield Federal Penitentiary,
獄警喬治·門德斯被逮捕
where the arrest of Correctional Officer George Mendez
他被起訴性侵犯  逮捕正在進行中
on charges of sexual assault is underway.
她來了
There she is!
我旁邊是娜塔莉·菲格羅亞
I'm here with Natalie Figueroa,
利奇菲爾德聯邦監獄的助理典獄長
Assistant Warden of Litchfield prison,
她是杰森·菲格羅亞的妻子
and wife of Jason Figueroa,
后者現正競選州參議員
who is currently running for state senate.
菲格羅亞夫人
Miss Figueroa,
你知道警員中有不當行為存在嗎
were you aware of misconduct among your officers?
在利奇菲爾德
Here at Litchfield,
我們對性罪犯者
we have a zero-tolerance
是絕對不會容忍的
policy when it comes to sexual offenders.
自《消除監獄強奸法案》頒布以來
Since the Prison Rape Elimination Act,
消除惡劣警員便成了我們的任務
we have made it our mandate to weed out rogue officers.
這些無助的女性在我們的照顧下
These vulnerable women are under our care,
我們會盡一切能力去保護她們
and we do everything in our power to protect them.
當然  這個世界上依然有壞人
Of course, there are still bad people in this world
會犯下十惡不赦的罪行
who commit heinous crimes,
不幸的是
and it is unfortunate that
其中一個道德敗壞的人  居然在我們這里
one of these sickos ended up under our roof.
但我向你保證  我們會盡一切力量
But I assure you, we are doing everything in our power
照顧這位年輕女性
to take care of this young woman,
她才是真正的受害者
who is the real victim here.
-等我  親愛的  -快走
- Wait for me, baby. - All right, keep it moving.
知道嗎  我不在乎了
You know what? I don't care anymore.
來吧  逮捕我
Go ahead, arrest me!
我愛這個女人
I love this woman!
你聽到我的話嗎
You hear me?
她懷的是我的寶寶  老子愛死你了
That is my baby in there, and I fucking love you!
我要給孩子取名叫斯坦  好嗎
I want to call it Stan, okay?
別舉重東西
Don't lift anything heavy!
別吃吞拿魚  也別吃軟芝士
And no tuna fish! Or soft cheese.
我會回來找你的  親愛的
I'm coming back for you, baby!
我會照顧你的  照顧你們母子
I'm gonna take care of you! Both of you!
快走  這里沒你事了
Let's go. You're done here.